{"data":[{"question":"I'm ________ to succeed.","a":"determinant","b":"determination","c":"determine","d":"determined","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be + determined + to do sth: having a strong desire to do something, so that you will not let anyone stop you.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The bird's egg is such an efficient structure for protecting the embryo inside ________ difficult for the hatchling to break.","a":"that is","b":"that","c":"and is","d":"that it is","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Such + noun phrase + that: used for emphasizing a particular quality in something or somebody stating its results\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"We had hoped ________ the game, but the other team played very well.","a":"state university to win","b":"that state university win","c":"that state university would win","d":"state university's winning","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Hope that + clause.\u00a0\n- Main clause in past perfect, subordinate clause will be past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The artistic medium of clay is ________ that images have been found near the remains of fires from the last ice age.","a":"so old","b":"such an old","c":"oldest","d":"old","answer":"1","explain":"\n- So\/such...that: used when emphasizing the degree or amount of something by saying what the result is.\n+ So + adj + that.\u00a0\n+ Such + noun phrase.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Unlike most Europeans, many Americans ________ a bowl of cereal for breakfast every day.","a":"used to eating","b":"are used to eat","c":"are used to eating","d":"use to eat","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be\/get used to (doing) something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"His body-guard will keep him safe ________ the crowded.","a":"from","b":"on","c":"to","d":"of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Keep somebody safe from.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The most common form of treatment ________ mass inoculation and chlorination of water sources.","a":"it is","b":"they are","c":"is","d":"are","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The subject (The most common form of treatment): is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"People with exceptionally high intelligence quotients may not be the best employees since they become bored ________ their work unless the job is constantly changing.","a":"of","b":"with","c":"in","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be\/become bored with sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither the mathematics department nor the biology department at state university requires that the students ________ a thesis in order to graduate with a master's degree.","a":"must write","b":"write","c":"will write","d":"would write","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Require\/ suggest\/recommend ...+ that + S + Infinitive (without to) + O.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"The oxygen content of mars is not ________ to support life as we know it.","a":"sufficient enough","b":"too sufficient","c":"enough sufficient","d":"sufficient","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sufficient: as much as is needed for a particular purpose (=enough).\u00a0\n- Be sufficient to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}